licensinglab.com 2005-03-16

# GYL Privacy Statement

Our commitment to security:  
We respect your right to privacy, and have developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our privacy practices for the entire web site. We share your concern in how companies use customer information. It is because of this concern that we will only use your information in a manner that respects your wishes and then only upon your express consent. Get Your License has employed physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the security and integrity of your personal information.

What personally identifiable information is collected:  
Get Your License collects the following types of personal information: names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and fax numbers.  
In compliance with the Childrens Online Protection Policy Act (COPPA), Get Your License does not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13, and no part of our sites are structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

What Organization Is Collecting the Information:  
Personal information is accessible only by our staff of representatives designated to handle online requests. All of our representatives who handle personal information obtained on our web site are bound to adhere to this commitment.

How is the information used:  
We will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted. We use personal information to conduct business with various state, and local agencies to obtain licensure and/or certification, and is only shared with these third parties with your explicit permission. We will never sell, rent or distribute your personal information to anyone for any reason.  
Our online forms are designed to automatically generate electronic mail responses to you; an electronic copy is automatically generated to our company representatives. By completing a form or sending us a request or inquiry, you are explicitly allowing us to forward your information to the appropriate company representative. Your email address will never be shared with any other company, organization without your consent. You can expect a phone call and/or email from our representatives upon completion of an online form.

Inquiry, Complaint, and Revisions:  
Our online forms are designed strictly to conduct business with our customers. If you need to add, delete, or revise your personal contact information, or submit a suggestion or complaint, please [ contact us ](mailto:info@gyl.com). Or you may, or course, call us at 888.542.7277 or locally 916.363.7466.

Cookies:  
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to analyze trends and administer the site. Additionally, this statistical information may also be provided to others, however, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. When you visit our site, our computers may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, but rather about a visit to our site. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our site, the user’s IP address, which pages people visit on our site, from which domains our visitors reach our site, and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our Web site. 

Links to us:  
Our web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

Shopping Cart:  
Our shopping cart services are authenticated by Thawte SSL Web Server Certificates to offer secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the site. SSL goes along with a Web Server Certificate that proves that the owner of the online business is who he says he is. The certificate can be viewed by clicking on the padlock in the bottom right-hand corner of your browser. With a trusted authority, like Thawte, you the customer can have confidence that you actually are sending confidential information to where you think you are sending it.

Forums:  
Be warned that disclosing personally identifiable information online through Forums makes the information submitted public information; such disclosure may increase your chance of receiving spam. Always be extra careful and use discretion when disclosing information online.
